ganeshaspeaks.com 2008-06-11

# Free Astrology, Free Horoscope by GaneshaSpeaks.com

|  |  |   
---  
  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

Privacy Policy

| We at SiddhiVinayak Astrology Services ("we" or "GaneshaSpeaks") have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. We realize the importance of feeling safe online and want you to feel comfortable using our personalized services and exchanging information on our web site. We are committed to protecting your personal information and will take reasonable steps to see that this privacy policy is followed within our company. This statement below outlines the privacy practices for GaneshaSpeaks.com and is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of our Terms of Service.  
---  
**Information collected**  
In order to provide you with personalized services and features we may ask you to register and establish your personal profile. During the registration process we may ask you for information such as your name, gender, birth information, e-mail address, password, place of residence, zip code, etc. This information is used to calculate an accurate horoscope or biorhythm and to provide you with the best possible personalized service. Your e-mail address together with a password is used to secure your profile and to make our personalized e-mail services available to you. We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities on our site through your IP address or most-recently-visited URL. However, we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by using our products and services or by filling out a form or survey.  
Personally identifiable information is collected primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the part of the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as name, gender, e-mail address, birth date, and birth location. Customers who personalize our service come back regularly, so we do everything we can to make GaneshaSpeaks.com your service and give you just the content you wish to receive.  
**Use of information**  
Demographic and profile data, as well as your registration data (i.e., e-mail address, gender, and password) is used to personalize our service to your interests and to deliver personalized information to you. For example, we may decide to use personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information for internal marketing purposes, for trend analysis, to better understand patterns of usage, and for site administration. Demographic and profile data is shared with our advertisers only on an aggregate basis. We might also share aggregated non-individually identifiable information about our users with our business partners. Aggregated data helps our advertisers to tailor their services to the collective characteristics of GaneshaSpeaks.com users. As a general practice, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information to third parties unless you give us your prior express consent. However, due to the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties under certain circumstances. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under court order, subpoena, or other circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to do so) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. In instances where we ask for your personally identifiable information and you are notified that the information we are collecting on that page will be shared with third parties, and in cases where you opt-in to share your information with third parties, those disclosures and opt-ins will override anything to the contrary in this privacy policy.  
**Use of ip addresses**  
We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and to track trends and statistics.  
**Use of cookies**  
When you view our web site or advertisements, we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive to facilitate your current and future visits to our site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, save passwords so you won't have to enter it each time you visit the site, and for other purposes. You can set your web browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept the cookie. However, some parts of the GaneshaSpeaks.com web site may not work properly if you deactivate or reject cookies.   
**Use of e-mail address**  
The e-mail address you submit to receive our services will never be disclosed to any third party. All horoscope e-mail that you select to receive as well as the special offers from our advertisers will be sent to you exclusively by GaneshaSpeaks.com.   
**Security**  
We DO NOT collect any payment information on our site. It is collected and processed in a secure manner by our payment gateway. The connection is 128 bit secure and the payment gateway is a Verisign secured site. Hereby we have implemented and follow reasonable industry standard technical and procedural measures to protect against unauthorized access and use of your personal information. However, you should know that neither we nor any other web site can fully eliminate these risks.   
**Other web sites links**  
Our web site may contain links to other web sites. GaneshaSpeaks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites.   
**Correct/update**  
You can change and update the personal information you previously provided. This may be done through the following method:   
1\. Click on the "Edit" link  
2\. Change the relevant information  
Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from our records. If you have chosen to receive your Daily or Weekly Horoscope by e-mail, you can at any time cancel this sending a mail on contact@ganeshaspeaks.com with the subject line as "Unsubscribe".   
**Delete profile**  
You can delete your profile at any time by clicking on the "delete" link.   
**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us at [contact@ganeshaspeaks.com](mailto:contact@ganeshaspeaks.com).  
  
home  
  
|  |   
  
|   
---  
|  | Testimonials |   
---|---|---  
|  | 

The language impresses me the most. It is a very mature, friendly advice which I get from this site

R. Srinivasan  
Chennai, India  
  
---  
  
* * *  
  
I am impressed with the product range of this site. I have ordered a few reports here and they are right on the dot when it comes to accuracy

Rajiv Chhabra  
London, England  
  
* * *  
  
If you want really quick horoscopes (within 72 hours), this is the site. I have always got all my forecasts in time

Rajesh Shah  
Toronto, Canada  
  
|  |
